Hi, in this FPD Insurance 101 session, I
want to share important things to
do [music]
and avoid when paying premiums or
contributions so that the policy remains active and the
protection for you, your family
remains safe.  First, when paying premiums
or contributions, pay according to the
total billed.
You can see the details of the [music] information
when you receive a
premium payment reminder notification from the
official FWD Insurance [music] email address or WhatsApp.
Avoid paying premiums or contributions
with a total that does not match the
bill.  Because it is possible that you will
overpay or underpay.
Second, make premium or
contribution payments according to the
official payment methods available at FD
Insurance [music] and according to what
you chose when you first applied for
insurance.  For those of you who choose the
auto debit payment method and the debate
fails at least once [music] and
you want to make
contribution premium payments using the non auto
debit method, then payment can be made
via the [music] Omni byy FWD application.   For
more information about
payments via the application, you can
check directly in the insurance menu of the
Omni byy FWD application.  [music]
And if you have any questions, please
contact FWD Insurance marketing staff
or FWD Customer Care directly.
Avoid making premium or
contribution payments other than with the
official payment methods available.  Make sure
premium payments are only made to the official account
of [music] F Insurance.  Third, especially
for those of you who choose the
auto-debit payment method, ensure that the
limit balance on your [music] credit card account is
sufficient for premium or
contribution payments and that you use a
credit card account registered with FWD
Insurance.  Avoid
misusing bank, account, and/
or credit card information that is appropriate and
has available limits to FD insurance
[music] so that it has an impact on the
contribution premium payment process.  Fourth,
currently the payment method that occurs
at FD Insurance [music] is via
transfer or auto debit.  To make things
easier for you, we recommend that
you update your payment method
to auto debit [music] so that
premium payments are made on time, the policy
remains active and protection is secure.
Fifth, always update the data.
For example, mobile phone number, email address,
and IKTP number at least once a year
.  To get
more optimal service and as soon as possible [music]
if there is a change in data, please avoid
changing the data
, sir, madam.   You can
easily access your data through the
insurance menu of the Omni by FWD application.  Sixth,
if you make a payment or
transfer to EVD insurance outside the
due date and
premium bill, you are required to
provide confirmation to FD Insurance
via FD Customer Care.
Avoid not providing
confirmation so that there is no condition of
your funds hanging and there is no
miscommunication between us.  See
you in the next FD 101.
Yeah.